Guide to the George B. Post Architectural Records circa 1860–1997 (bulk, 1880–1980) PR 53
New-York Historical Society
- Series VI. 2002 Accrual, 1894-1997; 354 Linear feet in 147 boxes.
  - Subseries VI.F. Rolled Drawings, 1936-1993; 291 Linear feet in 83 boxes.
    - 54-1132 | Blakeman (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-574)
    - 54-1133 | B. Rowland - Va. (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-574)
    - 54-1134 | Galston (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-574)
    - 54-1257 | Demerec (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-578)
    - 55-1137 | Heroy (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-557)
    - 55-1141 | Carfax (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-566)
    - 55-1143 | D. Lindsay Preums. File with [W. D.] (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-556)
    - 55-1144 | Gates J. (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-566)
    - 55-1146 | W. Peck Res. Tracings (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-566)
    - 55-1149 | R. Powers (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-566)
    - 55-1154 | "Losee" Volkswagen Sales and Services Bldg. (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-556)
    - 55-11[55] | S. O. Fuller (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-566)
    - 56-1155 | Ammidon Sr. (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-566)
    - 56-1156 | Merrit Quale Corp. (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-556)
    - 56-1164 | Rom Studios (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-566)
    - 56-1165 | Richard Storrs (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-555)
    - 56-1165 | Storrs L. R. (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-555)
    - 56-1169 | Murphy (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-556)
    - 56-1170 | Buttler (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-566)
    - 56-1172 | Victor (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-555)
    - 56-1172 | Victor (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-557)
    - 56-1178 | Potter Old House Alt. and Add. Not Built (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-557)
    - 57-1184 | Wardell (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-566)
    - 57-1186 | Bradley Collins (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-566)
    - 57-1188 | Val. Woods (Bay Window) Orig. Prints not G. B. P. and S. (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-555)
    - 57-1191 | Rumbough (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-557)
    - 57-1192 | Moss (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-556)
    - 57-1193 | Potter (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-556)
    - 57-1194-A and 57-1194-B | Village of Lloyd Habor (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-555)
    - 57-1203 | Sheeline (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-566)
    - 57-1205 | Bierrie Percy Weeks (garage apt. [west shane rd. [illegible]] | ([M] 28 78 - [illegible] - [Pasrott who died suddenly] - [inherited by [illegible] Bierrie] (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-566)
    - 57-1206 | Stone Res. Alts. C. S. H. (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-555)
    - 57-1206 | Post - Stone (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-570)
    - [58-1138] | [Hesslein] (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-566)
    - 58-1209 | Reynolds (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-557)
    - 58-1210 | Brookside Church (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-557)
    - 58-1215 | Ingram Tracings (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-557)
    - 58-1218 | Hawkhurst (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-557)
    - 58-1225 | Lipson Res. (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-557)
    - 58-1227 | Hoppin (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-557)
    - 58-1229 | Van Rensselear (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-555)
    - 58-1232 | Galehouse [Gatehouse?] (from Box 3) And 86-2152 | [illegible] (Offsite-box RD-555)
    - 58-2114 | Ingram (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-545)
    - 58-[unknown job number] | Cutting (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-553)
    - 59-1235 | L. I. B. A. Guest Bldg. (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-555)
    - 59-1238 | Floyd Blair (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-566)
    - 59-1239 | Swenson (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-571)
    - 59-1240 | Voorhees (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-566)
    - 59-1242 | L. I. B. A. James Lab (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-555)
    - 59-1[2]44 | Cold Spring Harbor [Methodist Ch.] (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-556)
    - 59-1247 | Belknap (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-557)
    - 59-1248 | Raymond French Originals and Tracings (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-556)
    - 59-12[48] | Ziegler (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-555)
    - 59-1252 | Stowe (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-566)
    - 59-1253 | Bates (from Box 4) 46-1012 (Offsite-box RD-553)
    - 59-1254 | Wayland (Brown) (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-557)
    - 59-1255 | St. John's Church Survey of Adj. Property Addition (from Box 3) 68-1528 | Church School Bldg. 70-[16??] | Entrance Landscaping 71-1684 and 71-1684A | Columbia 72-1748 | Dam Spillway (Offsite-box RD-556)
    - [59]-1257 | Demerel (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-566)
    - 59-1258 | Bleecker Res. (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-557)
    - 59-1259 | Stout (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-555)
    - 59-1262 | Martin Laurel Hollow (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-565)
    - 59-1263 | Warner (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-555)
    - 59-1265 | Jesse Knight (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-555)
    - [59]-1269 | S. D. Fuller (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-555)
    - 59-1270 | Sands and Additions (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-557)
    - 60-12[44] | L. I. B. A. Airsley House (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-551)
    - 60-1271 | Plimpton (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-553)
    - 60-1273 | L. I. B. A. Hooper House (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-559)
    - 60-1274 | Linder (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-552)
    - 60-1275 | Vill. of L. H. Beach House (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-551)
    - 60-1277 | Dudley addition to library (from Box 9) 70-1645 (Offsite-box RD-510)
    - 60-1278 | Dudley 1962 Addition (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-526)
    - 60-1278 | Lili B. A. (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-553)
    - 60-1282 | L. I. B. A. New Labs Tracings [illegible] Perspective ETC (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-552)
    - 60-1285 | [Balem] S. J. (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-551)
    - 60-1286 | Church Holy Trinity N. Y. C. (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-553)
    - 60-1287-A | L. I. B. A Bluckford Hall (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-551)
    - 60-1288 | Price add. west hills (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-551)
    - 60-[1]290 | CSH East Side School (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-552)
    - 60-1292 | Bowker (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-552)
    - 60-[1293] | Bernuth (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-553)
    - 60-1294 | L. I. B. A Childrens Science Bldg. Tracings (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-551)
    - 60-1296 | (L. I. B. A.) Urey Cottage (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-551)
    - 60-1297 | Elder (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-551)
    - 60-129[7] | D. Elder (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-551)
    - 60-1298 | Hubbard (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-552)
    - 60-1300 | R. D. Wood (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-553)
    - 61-1305 | Romaine (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-551)
    - 61-1306 | McHenry (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-543)
    - 61-1307 | Mrs. Quentin Roosevelt | and additions [and] topo. and survey | lav. added Dec 12 noted on print in file (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-553)
    - [61-1308] | N. Y. Airways (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-552)
    - 61-1310 | Johnston (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-552)
    - 61-1313 | Fuller (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-552)
    - 61-1314 | Paton (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-551)
    - 61-1315 | Olney St. James (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-551)
    - 61-1315 | Olney (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-554)
    - 61-1319 | Reed (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-551)
    - 61-1320 | Leach (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-551)
    - 61-1322 | Greenleaf (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-553)
    - 61-1323 | Alford Residence Arch. Tracings | see 68-1535 for addition (s. w.) and pool apparently started for Alford but titled by [Lootie] for [Baichll] | [includes plans for Essex residence bathing room, wrapped around the outside? - C. Osterhout] (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-551)
    - 61-1324 | Franz Schager Res. Mill River Road, Oyster Bay | old house blue prints guest house (for Mr. Dorrance - step father) 1963 | addition - tracings 1961 | proposed addition over study (1963) | elev. relocation (1971) | alts. to house at sagaponnack sketch of 2nd fl. rooms Dorrance house Oct. 4 1971 (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-551)
    - 61-1327 | Throop (from Box 4) (Also 46-[448]) (Offsite-box RD-551)
    - 61-[unknown job number] | Bleecker (Kirkland) (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-551)
    - 61-[unknown job number] | R. C. C. Drasher (from Box 4) (Offsite-box RD-551)
    - 62-1329 | Evan Thomas (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-546)
    - 62-133[0/3?] | Stewart Miller [?] (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-546)
    - 62-1332 | H. L. Williamson (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-543)
    - 62-1333 | W. Stewart (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-543)
    - 62-1335 | North Shore Holiday House Alt. and Cottages (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-546)
    - 62-1336 | Crocker (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-546)
    - 62-1337 | Biddle (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-543)
    - 62-1340 | Dwyer (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-546)
    - 62-1342 | Agnew (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-546)
    - 62-1343 | Keller Res. (alt. and add.) (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-546)
    - 62-1344 | E. F. Bateson Jr. (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-554)
    - 62-1345 | Frank Fuller (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-546)
    - 63-1346 | Twining (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-544)
    - 63-1349 | Rossiter (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-543)
    - 63-1350 | [A Ro(?)erdt Trelles (illegible) Bookcases] (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-544)
    - 63-1351 | St. Johns for [illegible] (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-543)
    - 63-1354 | Oneill (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-546)
    - 63-1355 | R. Berry Terr. (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-546)
    - [63]-1356 | Lytton Scott (from Box 3 of 4) 58-1221 (Offsite-box RD-571)
    - 63-1357 | Thortel (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-543)
    - 63-1359 | [Winper] Club (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-544)
    - 63-1361 | Stebbins (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-546)
    - 63-1364 | Fates (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-544)
    - 63-1367 | [Chas C. Townsend Jr Pool House and (illegible) (2 jobs) (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-544)
    - 63-1368 | Kelley Beach House (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-544)
    - 63-1369 | Del[a]field (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-543)
    - 63-1370 | Baldwin (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-543)
    - 63-1372 | Mundo L. Smith | sold to H[illegible] then to H[illegible] (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-544)
    - 63-1374 | John Nichols (ski lodge) (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-544)
    - 63-1377 | Olstein (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-526)
    - 63-1377 | Olstein (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-543)
    - 63-137[8] | Simone Tracings (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-543)
    - 63-1380 | Brown (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-554)
    - 64-1382 | McFlwain (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-544)
    - 64-1383 | Cox and Company Inc with Existing Conditions of 11th street and University Place (83-20[5]0) (from Box 5) 83-20[5]0 (Offsite-box RD-554)
    - 64-1384 | W. B. Nichols (from Box 5) 55-1152 (Offsite-box RD-543)
    - 64-1387 | Tilney (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-546)
    - 64-1390 | Hubbard (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-546)
    - 64-1391 | Alistair Martin Res. | Glen Head [cl] | measured existing conditions and prop. alts. | not executed | 1964 (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-546)
    - 64-1392 | Reed Clark (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-542)
    - 64-1394 | [Amyas] Ames (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-544)
    - 64-1395 | John Prentice Jennings | [oversize from various boxes] (Offsite-box RD-583)
    - 64-1396 | Stern (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-543)
    - 64-1397 | 1790 Shop - CSH (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-554)
    - 64-1400 | Hadley (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-546)
    - 64-1402 | Shedardson (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-546)
    - 64-1404 | Olsson (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-544)
    - 64-1406 | F. C. Smithers alts. overlook roads locust valley (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-544)
    - 64-1409 | Kirkbride (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-546)
    - 64-1416 | Watkins (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-543)
    - 64-1450 | Morrito 1/8" Preliminaries | James Leslie Jr. Factory [illegible] Road | Mill Neck, [L.] I. N. Y. (from Box 5) (Offsite-box RD-543)
    - 64-[unknown job number] | Hunt. Jr. H S (from Box 4 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-538)
    - [65-318] | W. M. [Floyd] Mastic H. S. Mech (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-581)
    - 65-1419 | Blydenburgh (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-542)
    - 65-1423 | Potter tracings (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-542)
    - 65-1424 | Onet (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-539)
    - 65-1427 | Ruekberg (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-542)
    - 65-1429 | Wood (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-540)
    - 65-1430 | Avery (from Box 6) [59]-1249 (Offsite-box RD-539)
    - 65-1431 | Crisp tracings (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-539)
    - 65-1432 | Dean (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-539)
    - 65-1435 | Robe, Robert S. (from Box 6) 69-1589 (Offsite-box RD-542)
    - 65-1436 | Harry Lee (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-542)
    - 65-1443 | Rousmaniere (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-539)
    - 65-1444 | Dudley Catskills (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-539)
    - 65-1445 | Scott - West Arlington VT (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-537)
    - 65-1446-8 [65-1446-B?] | Mrs. Geo Nichols (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-542)
    - 65-1447 | V. O. Post [illegible] (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-537)
    - 65-1448 | I. T. Willihills Lawrence [faded] (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-542)
    - 65-1449 | Titus (both jobs) (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-537)
    - 65-1450 | Mahan (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-542)
    - 65-1456 | Olmsted (from Box 5) 57-1207 (Offsite-box RD-554)
    - 65-1457 | Harbor Country Day School Corr. Add. and [Alt]. Gym Add. (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-537)
    - 65-1458 | Page (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-539)
    - 65-1587 | Rossiter, A. (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-517)
    - 65-4264 | Martin Dwyer porch enclosure and pool enclosure (from Box 6) 66-1460 (Offsite-box RD-542)
    - 65-[unknown job number] | Huntington senior high school (from Box 4 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-541)
    - 65-[unknown job number] | William Floyd Junior - Senior high school Mastic H S Arch. and St. (from Box 4 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-548)
    - [66-937] | Weekes (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-547)
    - 66-1460? | Dwyer R. W. Deforest Stable | prints of drawings by [illegible] no date | found in 80- | 66-1460? (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-540)
    - 66-1464 | Haynes prints of job also in this bin (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-537)
    - 66-1464 | Haynes prints, Bryan house, Pratt stable (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-540)
    - 66-1465 | Berry Res. Cold Springs Harbor (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-569)
    - 66-1468 | C. S. H. Library (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-540)
    - 66-1470 | Victoria Home Originals (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-539)
    - 66-1471 | Myers (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-539)
    - 66-1472 | Reverdin (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-540)
    - 66-1474 | Riley (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-542)
    - 66-1475 | Rectory Sch. Alt. and Add. N. W. Cottage M. D. B. Dorm (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-539)
    - 66-1475 | Rectory School gym and alt. (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-540)
    - 66-1477 | Campbell (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-542)
    - 66-1478 | Young (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-540)
    - 66-1478 | Young (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-542)
    - 66-1479 | Carr[field] (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-542)
    - 66-1484 | Horn [illegible] (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-537)
    - 66-1485 | Brower Store (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-539)
    - 66-1486 | Blair Res. (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-540)
    - 66-1491 | Straight Path (paumanok) misc. preliminaries and tracings (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-539)
    - 66-1491 | Tracings: Paumanok as Built (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-561)
    - H66-1491 | Straight Path Sepia Set to go to E. P. B[illegible] (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-572)
    - H66-1491 | Original Tracings Straight Path School Half Hollow Hills Pulminok (from unnumbered box) 66-1491 H66-101 (Offsite-box RD-581)
    - 66-[unknown job number] | Noyes (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-537)
    - 67-1442 | Pernel School [Howard Johnson] (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-506)
    - 67-1494 | [Adl. Skiclub of a. x.] (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-506)
    - 67-1495 | Powers Stormuille NY (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-506)
    - 67-1496 | Allen Preliminary (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-506)
    - 67-1498 | Herbert L. Smith (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-506)
    - 67-1500 | Abramson (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-505)
    - 67-1502 | [also 61-1318] | Goodwin (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-503)
    - 67-1504 | Brengle (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-503)
    - 67-1510 | Loud [Stanton] | [oversize from various boxes] (Offsite-box RD-583)
    - 67-1513 | Dean Residence Prints (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-504)
    - 67-1513 | A. H. Dean - Original Tracings | Preliminary (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-506)
    - 67-1516 | Chypre (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-504)
    - 67-1518 | Gatehouse (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-505)
    - 67-1518 | Gate House (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-506)
    - 67-1518 | Gate House (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-506)
    - 67-1519 | McIntyre Ski (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-503)
    - 67-1521 | Pulsifer (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-505)
    - 67-1522 | Pardee (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-505)
    - 67-1524 | Kronman (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-503)
    - 67-1525 | Bell (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-504)
    - 67-1525 | John C. Bell | Bell Site Topo. Survey Print (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-506)
    - 67-1558 | H. L. Smith (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-506)
    - 67-1611 | Geissler (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-505)
    - 68-1527 | Key (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-503)
    - 68-1528 | St. James (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-503)
    - 68-1529 | West Junior High School Original Mechanical Dwgs. Electrical "As Built" (from Box 4 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-548)
    - H68-1529 | Misc. Sketches and Prints West Jr. high (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-504)
    - H68-1529 | West Sr. High Misc. Sketches (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-505)
    - H68-1529 | West Junior High School Original Architectural and Structural (from Box 4 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-538)
    - H68-1529 | West Jr. H S Arch. and Struct. C. B.'s and Photo Posit. (from Box 4 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-548)
    - [H]68-1529 | West Jr. H. Preliminary Design Dwgs. (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-561)
    - H68-1529 | West Hill Jr. H. S. Preliminary | [oversize from various boxes] (Offsite-box RD-583)
    - 68-1532 | Mrs. E. F. Bates on Sr. (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-506)
    - 68-1535 | [Started for Alford then Baechle] | Residence for Mr. and Mrs. Robertson F. Alford (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-506)
    - 68-1536 | Galvin (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-506)
    - 68-1537 | Unique Site P G. S. H. (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-505)
    - 68-1538 | Howell, J. Taylor P. S. 4 pool [house] additions (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-504)
    - 68-1540 | McIntyre - Tracings Angus McIntyre All L. I. Jobs that were built (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-505)
    - 68-1540-A and 68-1540-B | McIntyre Barn - Garage Originals (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-505)
    - 68-1543 | Eisenman - Barn (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-503)
    - 68-1544 | Hoppih (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-503)
    - 68-1545 | Cold Spring Harbor Beach Club Survey Original Stanton, Walter Residence (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-503)
    - 68-1547 | J. Dudley New [windows in LR bay] with alts. Proposed addition to [DR] (not done?) (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-502)
    - 68-1547-B | Rudley Pool House (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-532)
    - 68-1549 | St. Marys add. to admin. offices (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-503)
    - 68-1549 | St. Mary's Hospital for children (from Box 6 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-507)
    - 68-1549 | St. Mary's hospital for children (from Box 6 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-507)
    - 68-1549 | St. Mary's hospital for children additions and alts. (from Box 6 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-507)
    - 68-1549 | CR and [Thurspy] St. Mary's Hospital Perspective (from Box 6 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-508)
    - 68-1549 | St. Mary's Studies [re working drawing] CR and [Thruspy] Wing (from Box 6 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-508)
    - [68-1549] | St. Mary's Hospital Kronaflex negatives proposed additions layouts | flame tested safe 2019 (from Box 6 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-508)
    - 68-1549 | St. Mary's Hospital location of fire stations (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-509)
    - 68-1549 | St. Mary's hospital for children (with schemes with unknown job number) (from Box 6 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-523)
    - 68-1549 | St. Mary's hospital for children Kronaflex Negatives original bldg. layouts (from Box 6 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-524)
    - 68-1551 | [Tracings Otseg] and Forest Park (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-561)
    - 68-1552 | Wehle (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-505)
    - 68-1553 | Schecter Res. - pool (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-506)
    - 68-1554 | Kline (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-503)
    - 68-1559 | Middendorf (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-506)
    - 68-1560 | Prints and sketches of Vanderbilt School (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-504)
    - 68-1560 | North Park Sepias Gen. Const. and Mechanical (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-581)
    - H68-1560 | North Park School (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-561)
    - 68-1562 | Pickering (from Box 7) 69-1598 (from Box #7) 70-1641 (from Box #7) (Offsite-box RD-506)
    - 68-1563 | Doubleday (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-504)
    - 68-1564 | John Tilney - Tilney Alteration - original (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-506)
    - 68-1565 | Bilkey (from Box 7) (Offsite-box RD-506)
    - 68-1639 | Rectory School M. G. B Dorm Drawings for Auditorium [illegible] | [oversize from various boxes] (Offsite-box RD-583)
    - [68-1682] | Eastwoods Surveys (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-550)
    - 69-1569 | Wood and J. Woods garage apartment orig. and prints (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-514)
    - 69-1571 | Brush Homestead Orig. and Prints (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-509)
    - 69-1572 | Huntington Country Club (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-517)
    - 69-1573 | Haskel Swain (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-509)
    - 69-1574 | Colihan (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-509)
    - 69-1575 | Dr. Weidel (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-563)
    - 69-1575 | Dr. and Mrs. Philip Wiedel (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-564)
    - 69-157[8] | Burton Lee (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-516)
    - H69-1579 | Ford Motor Co. (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-509)
    - H69-1579 | I. T. Williams Hillsdale [md 85-2130] (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-509)
    - 69-1582 | Truslow (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-517)
    - 69-1584 | Lamont Mahoney (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-516)
    - H69-1586 | Bagatelle Road School Original Architectural Mechanical and Structural (from Box 4 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-538)
    - 69-1587 | Lee (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-514)
    - 69-1588 | Christ Church [Manhasset] originals and tracings (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-516)
    - 69-1594 | Mercedes Benz - [Smithtown] (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-514)
    - H69-1594 | Mercedes Benz [71-1655] (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-514)
    - 69-1597 | Pearshall (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-516)
    - 69-1601 | Parsons Jr. Tracings (from unnumbered box) 73-1718 78-1940 82-2047 and 2050 89-2221-A and 89-2221-B (Offsite-box RD-564)
    - H69-1602 | Hatcher Act. And Had. | [hospital for sk-20] (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-516)
    - 69-1603 | Mrs. Douglas Williams (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-516)
    - 69-1604 | Monroe (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-521)
    - 69-1607 | Mahoney (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-509)
    - 69-1609 | 3 Harbor Road Building | dean prints (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-516)
    - 70-1610 | David Clark Sepia (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-517)
    - 70-1612 | Clarkson (from Box 8) 74-1794 (Offsite-box RD-514)
    - 70-1613 | Prescott Jennings (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-509)
    - 70-1614 | Nichols, W. | Mrs. WM B Laurel Hollow | Topo and Subdivision Maps and Schemes | plus prelims. and working dwgs. for residence | abandoned when Mrs. [Nichols] married de Kay (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-517)
    - 70-1615 | Mitchell Cadillac (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-501)
    - 70-1616 | Messner (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-509)
    - 70-1618 | Bigelow (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-501)
    - 70-1619 | R. V. Lindsay (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-514)